<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A blog from code space</title><link>https://yordan.llc/</link><description>Recent content on A blog from code space</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yordan.llc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Making Remote Work Work</title><link>https://yordan.llc/posts/why-i-work-remotely/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/posts/why-i-work-remotely/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fully remote work is here to stay, even if it does not become as ubiquitous as it was in 2022. While there are many companies out there that have fully returned all their employees back to the office for fully in-person work, there will always be a market of employee and employees that will prefer to reach a working agreement that is location agnostic. This might not be possible to achieve for all companies across all industries, but I firmly believe that remote work is ultimately better than in-person work for most companies that mainly perform business over the internet.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://yordan.llc/services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 15:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/services/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="open-to-contract-or-full-time-roles">Open to Contract or Full-Time Roles&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Do you want me to be part of your team ? I cannot guarantee my availability for full-time work but I am open to network for future opportunities or part-time remote work.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="hands-on-project-work">Hands On Project Work&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Schedule a free consultation with me to go over the problem that you need solving. I will discuss with you potential solutions, and if applicable a free discovery call to understand the challenges that we may face together.
I will provide a value based priced proposal for the final deliverable custom fit to your specific needs.
Ideal for those that need a short term project done but do not have the budget for staffing a temporary development team.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>1. Acceptance of Terms&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By requesting or engaging in services provided by Fernando Yordan LLC (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;), you (&amp;ldquo;the Client&amp;rdquo;) hereby agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth in this document. Fernando Yordan LLC offers professional services encompassing software consultancy and development.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>2. Scope of Work and Project Commencement&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The scope of work for each client and project may vary. Accordingly, the Client agrees to thoroughly review all documentation detailing the scope of work, associated costs, and project timelines before the commencement of any services. Fernando Yordan LLC will not seek compensation for consultations, quotes, discovery sessions, or interviews explicitly designated as free. Billable work will only commence upon mutual agreement and signature of a formal engagement document.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>1. Introduction&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Fernando Yordan LLC (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) is committed to protecting the privacy and sensitive data of its clients and website visitors (&amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;rdquo;). This Privacy Policy outlines our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your information.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>2. Information Collection and Use&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We collect information solely for the purpose of providing and improving our consulting and software development services. We will only use the information you provide to us to fulfill our obligations to you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://yordan.llc/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is my first post.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Only meant to show I can&lt;/p>
&lt;p>write a simple blog.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://yordan.llc/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>I enjoy solving problems and am well versed with modern technologies in the field of AI, Machine Learning, Cloud Computing, Systems Engineering, DevOps, and Data Engineering, as well as building high performing technology teams with Generative Cultures in Agile environments. With experience as both an IC in companies like Google and Amazon, as well as a CTO in a Technology Startup, I understand how to scale bootstrap solutions to fully capable commercial products and teams.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>