<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A blog from code space</title><link>https://yordan.llc/</link><description>Recent content on A blog from code space</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 15:35:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yordan.llc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Services</title><link>https://yordan.llc/services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 15:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/services/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="open-to-contract-or-full-time-roles">Open to Contract or Full-Time Roles&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Do you want me to be part of your team ? I cannot guarantee my availability for full-time work but I am open to network for future opportunities or part-time remote work.
Schedule an Interview with me.
Hands On Project Work
Schedule a free consultation with me to go over the problem that you need solving. I will discuss with you potential solutions, and if applicable a free discovery call to understand the challenges that we may face together.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</guid><description>&lt;p>By requesting services from Fernando Yordan LLC the customer sequentially agrees to the terms in this document. Fernando Yordan LLC is a company that provides professional services in the form of consultancy and software development. The scope of work can be different for each client and each project, and as such the customer agrees to review any documentation detailing the scope of work and costs associated with each project before commencing work. Fernando Yordan LLC will not seek compensation for any consultation, quote, discovery, or interview labeled as free, but will require signature and agreement of terms before commencing billable work.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fernando Yordan LLC respects the customer&amp;rsquo;s privacy and their sensitive data. Fernando Yordan LLC will only use information provided to them in order to serve the customer providing said information. In the case information needs to be shared in order to perform services, Fernando Yordan LLC will seek authorization to do so beforehand. Fernando Yordan LLC will not seek any information that is not necessary to perform or improve their services.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://yordan.llc/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is my first post.
Only meant to show I can
write a simple blog.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://yordan.llc/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>I enjoy solving problems and am well versed with modern technologies in the field of AI, Machine Learning, Cloud Computing, Systems Engineering, DevOps, and Data Engineering, as well as building high performing technology teams with Generative Cultures in Agile environments. With experience as both an IC in companies like Google and Amazon, as well as a CTO in a Technology Startup, I understand how to scale bootstrap solutions to fully capable commercial products and teams.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>