<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on A blog from code space</title><link>https://yordan.llc/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on A blog from code space</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:53:32 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yordan.llc/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Working Agreements and Why I won't Return to Office</title><link>https://yordan.llc/posts/why-i-work-remotely/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:53:32 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/posts/why-i-work-remotely/</guid><description>&lt;p>I don&amp;rsquo;t do well with daily routines, specially if that daily routine includes sitting in traffic just to sit in a cubicle in front of my laptop (which works just as well at home, or in another country as it does in the office). I don&amp;rsquo;t deny that there is value to routine and in-person work, but there&amp;rsquo;s more value in working for the life we want than there is in living for the work we have. A life with the freedom to choose where and how we work is better than a life that shaped by our work.&lt;/p></description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I don&rsquo;t do well with daily routines, specially if that daily routine includes sitting in traffic just to sit in a cubicle in front of my laptop (which works just as well at home, or in another country as it does in the office). I don&rsquo;t deny that there is value to routine and in-person work, but there&rsquo;s more value in working for the life we want than there is in living for the work we have. A life with the freedom to choose where and how we work is better than a life that shaped by our work.</p>
<p>For some, in-person work provides the work-life balance and the means to an end, if not the end itself, for the fulfillment that they desire. For me, any job that prevents me from spending &ldquo;enough&rdquo; time with my family or gets in the way of finding fulfillment can only be a means to survive until a better means presents itself. It is a shame that my interests lie in work that typically demands in-person work. I cannot deny that it would be easier to work in a robotics company if I could see and interact with the robots themselves, or that the conversations that happen around the office coffee machine can be a catalyst for collaboration and innovation. With many of the companies I follow wanting their employees to return to office, I know that if I only wanted to maximize my chances of working on a project I enjoy and getting paid handsomely to do so, then the optimum move would be to pack my bags and move back to California. However, I know that such a path will guarantee that I will regret not having spent &ldquo;enough&rdquo; time with my grandparents in their lifetime. This is why I left Google after my grandmother passed away during the covid 19 pandemic. Being near my family was significantly more valuable than showing up to an office to work by myself.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>It&rsquo;s a long flight from San Francisco to a funeral in Puerto Rico. When family and friends are content with what they have, it&rsquo;s an expensive way to realize you could have been too.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Since life and its needs are fluid, so are the expectations and requirements one puts when evaluating any sort of career change.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://yordan.llc/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is my first post.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Only meant to show I can&lt;/p>
&lt;p>write a simple blog.&lt;/p></description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my first post.</p>
<p>Only meant to show I can</p>
<p>write a simple blog.</p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>