<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legaleses on A blog from code space</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/</link><description>Recent content in Legaleses on A blog from code space</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yordan.llc/legalese/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</guid><description>&lt;p>By requesting services from Fernando Yordan LLC the customer sequentially agrees to the terms in this document. Fernando Yordan LLC is a company that provides professional services in the form of consultancy and software development. The scope of work can be different for each client and each project, and as such the customer agrees to review any documentation detailing the scope of work and costs associated with each project before commencing work. Fernando Yordan LLC will not seek compensation for any consultation, quote, discovery, or interview labeled as free, but will require signature and agreement of terms before commencing billable work.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fernando Yordan LLC respects the customer&amp;rsquo;s privacy and their sensitive data. Fernando Yordan LLC will only use information provided to them in order to serve the customer providing said information. In the case information needs to be shared in order to perform services, Fernando Yordan LLC will seek authorization to do so beforehand. Fernando Yordan LLC will not seek any information that is not necessary to perform or improve their services.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>