<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legaleses on A blog from code space</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/</link><description>Recent content in Legaleses on A blog from code space</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yordan.llc/legalese/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/tos/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>1. Acceptance of Terms&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By requesting or engaging in services provided by Fernando Yordan LLC (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;), you (&amp;ldquo;the Client&amp;rdquo;) hereby agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth in this document. Fernando Yordan LLC offers professional services encompassing software consultancy and development.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>2. Scope of Work and Project Commencement&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The scope of work for each client and project may vary. Accordingly, the Client agrees to thoroughly review all documentation detailing the scope of work, associated costs, and project timelines before the commencement of any services. Fernando Yordan LLC will not seek compensation for consultations, quotes, discovery sessions, or interviews explicitly designated as free. Billable work will only commence upon mutual agreement and signature of a formal engagement document.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 02:46:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yordan.llc/legalese/privacy/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>1. Introduction&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Fernando Yordan LLC (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) is committed to protecting the privacy and sensitive data of its clients and website visitors (&amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;rdquo;). This Privacy Policy outlines our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your information.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>2. Information Collection and Use&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We collect information solely for the purpose of providing and improving our consulting and software development services. We will only use the information you provide to us to fulfill our obligations to you.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>